come inequality,
you
yellow
are facing the direction
a ringer,
a ringer, a ringer
So this is Saudi Arabia.
About 8,800 kilometers from Japan.
And it's been around four weeks
since we began our journey.
If we don't hurry, we'll
be in serious trouble.
Kakyoin.
Hey, Jotaro
What do you think is up with Kakyoin?
First he nearly kills us in his sleep.
Now he looks like he's
coming apart at the seams.
He even went after the baby.
Something's just not right.
If you ask me, he's at his wit's end.
I hate to say it, I really do.
But we may have to send him packing.
For a second there I thought
he'd actually figured me out
but now the poor louse is half
doubting himself to top things
off we're in the middle of
the desert all I have to do is
wait until they fall asleep if
there's no one to wake them up.
Something smells good.
What kind of food is that?
This is baby food.
It's a delicious concoction of milk,
egg yolks, bananas and
bread, all stewed together.
So you want to taste it?
Easy now.
At this rate there won't
be any left for the baby.
You incompetent bastard!
How dare you eat my food?
I'm wasting away over here, so
hurry up and feed me, dammit!
Ah! It's...
it's a scorpion!
What am I going to do?
That was a close one.
Crap baskets!
Kakyoin was watching!
He killed the scorpion.
So I was right.
That baby really is a... Shit! What now?
You're not getting any more.
Mr. Joestar. Polnareff!
Did you see that?
I was right after all.
That baby's not normal.
He just killed a scorpion!
He stabbed it!
The boy skewered it
with his own safety pin!
Kakuine, hold on a sec.
What the hell are you talking about?
A baby, damn it.
That kid is a human.
He's not even a year old yet.
But he knew what a scorpion was.
And he killed it with
those tiny hands of his.
A scorpion?
Where is it? It's in here.
Where did it go?
There should be an impaled scorpion here!
It's gone.
I swear it's true.
He must have hidden it somewhere!
Check his clothes!
We get the point.
Knock it off, Kakyoin.
That's enough. Mr. Joestar!
Like I said before, you're
clearly exhausted. But...
Let's table this.
At least for tonight.
We'll talk after you've calmed down.
Huh?
OK, here's the Shuichi.
It's delicious!
Uh-oh.
What's the matter?
You were hungry a minute ago, right?
Did you lose that big appetite?
Ah? Huh?
Would you stop shoving
that spoon in my face?
I can't eat right now, you idiot!
Mr.
Joestar, listen, I'm not imagining things.
I don't know where he could have
hidden the blasted scorpion,
but I'm sure that he's a stand user.
And I have just the thing to prove to you
that I'm telling the truth.
Do you see these cuts?
Read what the letters spell out.
Can't you see that it's a warning?
It must have happened to me
when I was sleeping earlier.
Oh, my God!
Kakyoin, you didn't do that to
yourself, did you? Say what?
It's finally happened. Kakyoin.
Oh, my God!
You colossal buffoon!
How stupid can you be?
Didn't you realize if you showed
them the cuts on your arm,
they'd think you were crazy?
What's going on?
Did I make things even worse?
Then it looks like I have no other choice.
It's time for a little force.
I revenge Green!
It's no use. Damn it.
The guy's completely lost his mind.
This can't be happening.
I'm certain of what I saw.
Ah, Jotaro, his stand was the one
we fought in our dreams, Polnareff.
We can't fall asleep, Mr.
Joestar.
Believe me, everyone.
If we fall asleep, we'll all be killed.
Please, you have to believe me.
Yes, my secret is still safe,
which means the end is near.
Your petty mistrust just
cost you your lives.
Victory is mine, fools.
I can't believe it.
If he's like this, does that mean Kakyoin
can't fight or travel with us anymore?
We'll discuss it in the morning.
Let's get some sleep.
Polnareff, give me a hand
moving Kakyoin. Sure thing.
Jotaro, you bring the
sleeping bags. Right.
You say something?
No, he's just really heavy.
I've got you right where I want you.
I'm gonna slice you up and scatter
your remains all over the desert.
What in the world why
are we in the middle of
an amusement park we were
just out in the desert?
That's right i know this
place Dotero Mr Joestar
be on your guard my memory
is coming back we've
been transported to a
dream world a horrible one
this is bad we've entered
a world of nightmares.
Oh, so it's a dream, huh?
You had me a little
worried for a minute there.
Don't make the same mistake that I did!
Listen, everything Kakyoin
said to us earlier is true.
Baby, stand.
We are in enemy territory.
I know none of this makes any kind of
sense, but the stand user is that baby.
There's no one left to wake
you from your slumber now,
And that means there's absolutely no
way for you to escape Death 13's world!
I'll finally finish you
off once and for all!
Why did I have to hit
Kakyoin and knock him out?
But since I did that, he
should already be here!
We've got to find him!
Where in the world are you, Kakyoin?
I have to find a way
to make this up to you!
Polareff, good lord!
What is going on with your hair?
Did you mess up brushing it? Huh?
Polareff!
What the?
What's going on?
My prosthetic hand is...
Holy shit, Bricks!
How are we supposed to fight this?
It's maddening!
Damn, anything can happen in this world.
There are no rules here.
Nothing makes sense.
As long as we're in this place,
we're completely at his mercy.
Wait, I remember there being one rule.
His murder weapon.
Then, if he wants to slice us to pieces,
then he'll have to use his stand.
And nothing but his stand!
Lali-hoo!
Hurrah! Star!
Jotaro, it's no use!
It's impossible for us to bring
our stands into this world!
Platinum!
That's weird.
His stand manifested.
Hurrah?
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Lally-ho!
Surprise, I'm a fake!
Oh, the overwhelming power!
The absolute terror!
It's so much fun!
A stand is a manifestation of the mind.
And what are dreams if
not the mind laid bare?
My death 13 has trapped you
within your subconscious.
which is why you can't
summon your precious stands.
Although,
things might be different had you summoned
your stands before you fell asleep.
Then they would have appeared here with
you, just like your clothes, sleeping bags,?
and your prosthetic hand.
Death 13 will never be forced
to face another stand in battle.
And as you know, the only thing that
can defeat a stand is another stand.
so I'll always come out on top!
Now that I have all of you in my
crosshairs, how about you give me a scream?
One that captures the joy and elation
I'm about to feel in my easy victory!
Loli! Oh?
Loli-ho.
Oh, it's just one of the fakes I made.
What?
I don't understand!
This one doesn't seem to be a fake!
This is the real Hierophant!
It's normal!
Look, it's Kakueen!
Kakueen's right there!
Obviously, it slipped your notice that
I'd already summoned my Hierophant.
by the time I was knocked unconscious.
What's more, I had to burrow underground?
to conceal itself from detection.
just before I fell asleep.
You can't do this!
Now it's time for your punishment, baby.
Damn that bastard!
Let's go!
Give up, Death.
I had Hierophant place
himself in your blind spot.
If you keep up this futile struggling,
I really don't care that you're a baby.
I'll snap your neck like a twig. Kakyoin!
Kakyoin, the three of us
owe you an enormous apology.
I thought after the hell you'd
been through on this trip,
you might have suddenly lost your sanity.
I mean, a baby stand user?
You were fighting this battle alone.
And for that, I'm sorry.
Don't worry, Polnareff.
It couldn't have been helped.
You were the reason I found a way to
bring my stand to the dream world with me.
If you hadn't hit me, we'd be stuck
here without a way to defend ourselves.
So, in a way, this is
all thanks to you. Yeah?
Do you mean that?
Gee, now I feel conflicted
about the whole thing!
That's embarrassing!
Kakyoin hasn't killed me
yet because I'm a baby.
Kakyoin, that compassion
of yours is a fatal flaw.
In case you've forgotten, you're all
still trapped inside my nightmare world.
Uh-oh what's up with these clouds?
No kidding they're changing
shape and closing in!
I'm warning you now don't
try anything death 13!
You have to get hierophant away
from his back before it's too late.
Pouted!
I'll chop you in half!
Impossible!
How could he do that?
He...
he chopped himself in half!
Kick! No!
Lally-ho!
Haven't you figured it out yet?
Death-13's body is as hollow
as the space between your ears!
My stand is only comprised of the head,
arms, and the giant siphon wheels!
You gigantic ignoramuses!
Let's see,
given the way the stands work,
Kakyoin's body should also be split
in two inside the sleeping bag.
Nah, just kidding.
Kakyoin!
Hey, you sure you're all right?
Ha, please take a closer look.
Surely you know Hierophant
isn't that careless.
He wouldn't just stay on the enemy's
back without a plan in the wings.
He's not chopped in half.
He's turned into a snake-like thing,
and he's slithering into my ear!
Oh, my arm is moving on its own!
No, it's coming in!
I told you before,
my stand was in your blind spot,
and your scythe couldn't cut him.
Now then, unless you'd like to
be destroyed from the inside out,
how about you do me a favor
and heal the cuts on my arm?
Anything is possible in a dream, right?
So healing a cut should be easy
All right, everyone.
Time to wake up
Come on, Polnareff. Up and at him.
There's a nice breakfast waiting for you
I feel like I had a
terrible dream last night.
You and me both.
I can't remember it, but I have the
sneaking suspicion that it was terrifying.
Kakuin!
Are you okay? How are you feeling?
I'm fine. What?
Are you positive?
Because you were acting like
a deranged lunatic last night.
You even carved letters in your arm.
Wait, what?
Where did the wound go?
All right.
I think I'll change the baby's diaper now.
What in the world?
It's morning, sleepyhead.
He seems to be getting along
famously with the baby.
Maybe I just dreamed the whole thing.
Well then, did you have a good rest?
Oh, well, never mind.
Mm-hmm.
Everyone's forgotten.
A stand whose very existence
is completely forgotten.
What a strange creature.
But I haven't forgotten anything.
Since I brought my stand into the
dream with me, my memories are intact.
Listen, because you're just a
baby, I won't eliminate you.
I won't even injure you.
We'll take you to a nearby town.
You need to be returned to your mother.
However, don't come
anywhere near us again.
If you do, you'll have to be punished.
In a manner such as this.
Is that my poop?
Oh, Cochulein, I see you've made
some baby food for the little lad.
Yes, good work.
I'm sure he must be starving by now.
Hey, no, you wouldn't!
Eat up!
These yum-yums are delicious!
Say-yum!
This again?
What's the problem?
It's as if he doesn't like this stuff.
At this rate, I'll have to force-feed him.
Stop!
You can't force it, Mr. Joestar.
If you do, he'll just end
up hating it even more.
In special cases like this.
I told you it was delicious.
Joestar and the others have now
crossed the Arabian Peninsula
and are currently making
their way across the Red Sea?
as they prepare to enter Egypt. But!
Hey, old man.
Something's off.
You're going the wrong direction.
If you're headed to Egypt, shouldn't
you be traveling directly west? Hmm?
You seem to be heading toward that island.
That's right. Nice deduction.
I've had my reasons for
keeping this to myself.
But before we arrive in Egypt,
we need to make a slight detour.
Someone is waiting for us on the island.
Hmm.
He's a man who is extremely
important to our journey.
What is that supposed to mean?
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If you move too quick!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got the money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Fallen types with a hookah.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings!
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian?
I ended up killing my friend.
There's nothing I could possibly do.
Allow me to thank you for
freeing me from the lab.
I wouldn't believe it
if it wasn't right here.
Tell me your three wishes.
Do you have the ability to revive someone?